Try searching for:

Products

Explore Mural AI & the MSFT 365 Copilot integration

Experience a better way to work with Mural AI and the Microsoft 365 Copilot integration.

Solutions

.webp)

Find out how well your team works

Mural has solutions to help all teams thrive. See where your team stands with the Mural Teamwork Assessment.

Enterprise

.webp)

Help teams work better across the enterprise

Great teamwork is no accident. Understand your team’s needs with the Mural Teamwork Assessment.

Resources

Does your team need work?

The state of teamwork is ... not great. Learn why workers and leaders are feeling the heat in our research report.

Search

Sign in

[‍

Sign up free](https://app.mural.co/signup)

Privacy Statement
=================

Terms

Policies

Security

More

Subscribe to Subprocessor Updates  

------------------------------------

Thank you! Your submission has been received! 🎉

Something went wrong while submitting the form.

Subprocessor  

Subprocessing Activities  

Location  

Adobe  

Cloud-based Marketing Automation Solution  

United States  

Amazon Web Services  

Cloud Service Provider  

United States  

Chorus  

Cloud-based Analytics Tool  

United States  

Fivetran  

Cloud Based Connector and Data Centralization Services  

United States  

Mandrill / Mailchimp  

Cloud-based Customer Support Services  

United States  

Microsoft Azure  

Cloud Service Provider  

United States  

MongoDB, Inc  

Cloud database Service Production Database  

United States  

Salesforce Cloud  

Cloud-based Customer Support Services  

United States  

Twilio Inc, dba “Segment”  

Customer Data Platform  

United States  

Amplitude  

Cloud Based Product Analytics Service  

United States  

New Relic  

Cloud Based Product Analytics Service  

United States  

Last Updated: October 17, 2024  

Mural is committed to transparency about our collection, use, transfer and disclosure of your information. Please direct any inquiries, comments or questions regarding this Privacy Statement or our processing of your information to: [privacy@mural.co](mailto:privacy@mural.co).  

This Privacy Statement describes how Mural processes personal information, and what choices individuals have with respect to their personal information. By accessing and using a Mural product or service, you are agreeing to the practices and policies described in this Privacy Statement. If you object to any practices or policies as described in this Privacy Statement, please do not access or use our Services.  

{{privacy-statement-download="/utility/styleguide/legal-components"}}

{{privacy-statement-cta="/utility/styleguide/legal-components"}}

* Products

* Solutions

* Resources

* Company

* Our Apps

* Social

* [
    
    Your Privacy Choices](#)

* © 2024 Mural. All rights reserved.
    
* LUMA Institute, LLC is a wholly-owned subsidiary of Tactivos, Inc. d/b/a Mural.  
    The Mural name and logo are trademarks of Tactivos, Inc. dba Mural.
